[
    { "question": "", "answer": "" },
    {
        "question": "They found a number of diseases in the___of the local animals they examined.",
        "answer": "livers"
    },
    {
        "question": "The hunters here used to use large metal___to catch wild animals.",
        "answer": "traps"
    },
    {
        "question": "The___of our wild animals depends on everyone helping to keep our natural areas clean.",
        "answer": "conservation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hunters used to sell___skins for use in wallets and boots.",
        "answer": "anteater"
    },
    {
        "question": "Many of the___animals in this area have been captured or killed.",
        "answer": "endemic"
    },
    {
        "question": "My cellphone is my most___possession. I don't know what I'd do without it.",
        "answer": "prized"
    },
    {
        "question": "I'm so angry about your question that I don't think I give you a___answer.",
        "answer": "dignified"
    },
    {
        "question": "The scientists have been working on new types of___that don't harm the environment.",
        "answer": "pesticides"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forests and jungles have a lot more___than deserts.",
        "answer": "biodiversity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Be careful walking in that part of the forest; there are lots of bear___hidden there.",
        "answer": "traps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Did you know that we have a program to help our___population?",
        "answer": "anteater"
    },
    {
        "question": "The basketball player had to quit the game because of his___.",
        "answer": "injuries"
    },
    {
        "question": "You know that smoking causes damage to your___, so why do you do it?",
        "answer": "lungs"
    },
    {
        "question": "The air in winter is really dry, and it can make your skin___and itchy if you don't take care of it.",
        "answer": "scaly"
    },
    {
        "question": "There are a lot of___types of animals on this mountain.",
        "answer": "endemic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Gold is___for both its beauty and its use in electronics.",
        "answer": "prized"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hundreds of thousands of sharks are killed___each year.",
        "answer": "globally"
    },
    {
        "question": "China has had great success in stopping the___of its pandas.",
        "answer": "extinction"
    },
    {
        "question": "He had several___from his motorcycle accident.",
        "answer": "injuries"
    },
    {
        "question": "As soon as we got off the train, our___filled with fresh air.",
        "answer": "lungs"
    },
    {
        "question": "That animal has___skin to protect it from being attacked.",
        "answer": "scaly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Don't worry if you have a broken heart right now. Young people are___, and you'll find someone else to love after a while.",
        "answer": "resilient"
    },
    {
        "question": "Drinking too much alcohol can harm the___of the people who do it for a long period of time.",
        "answer": "livers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Water pollution is not only an issue here; it's also a problem___.",
        "answer": "globally"
    },
    {
        "question": "It takes a lot of___to become a movie star, so don't give up!",
        "answer": "perseverance"
    },
    {
        "question": "The zookeepers were able to create a very successful tiger___program.",
        "answer": "breeding"
    },
    {
        "question": "All of the fish in the river died due to the___caused by the factory.",
        "answer": "pollution"
    },
    {
        "question": "I didn't pass my driving test last week, but I've decided to be___about it, and I'll try again next week.",
        "answer": "resilient"
    },
    {
        "question": "The queen spoke to the people of her country in a very kind and___way.",
        "answer": "dignified"
    },
    {
        "question": "As the people moved into the area, the animal___became much smaller.",
        "answer": "habitat"
    },
    {
        "question": "The farmers here have been___chickens that can produce extra large eggs.",
        "answer": "breeding"
    },
    {
        "question": "Air___in big cities is the cause of many deaths each year.",
        "answer": "pollution"
    },
    {
        "question": "The people of this area work together to protect the___of the lake.",
        "answer": "biodiversity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Local___groups have been working for years to make sure that the birds are protected from hunters.",
        "answer": "conservation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Many types of butterflies are___each year due to climate change.",
        "answer": "disappearing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Don't give up! Learning a new language sometimes requires a lot of___.",
        "answer": "perseverance"
    }
]